dlpng.com 2019-10-30

# Terms of Service - DLPNG.com

#### Collection of personal information

You have been informed and agree that when you register for the Dlpng user account or use the services provided by Dlpng, Dlpng will record relevant personal information provided by you, such as your name, mobile number, etc. The above personal information is the basis for your access to the services provided by Dlpng. Besides this, for the purpose of optimizing user experience, Dlpng will obtain other information related to improving the services of Dlpng. For example, when you access Dlpng, we may collect the popularity of these services, browser software information, and so on to optimize our services.

#### Personal information management

In order to provide you with better services and products, Dlpng will use your personal information in the following situations:

1\. In accordance to the requirements of relevant laws and regulations;

2\. In accordance to your authorization;

3\. In accordance to the Dlpng receipt section related service terms and application license user agreement.

In addition, you are aware that and agree that Dlpng may use your non-private personal information for marketing within the scope permitted by current laws and regulations. Possible uses include but are not limited to: showing you in the Dlpng platform or providing advertising and promotional materials, recommending you and notifying you of Dlpng services and product information, and other such usages of Dlpng services or products that you may find interesting based on the information. It also includes information that you choose to share when you take an action such as authorization, such as when you add a new address book, download and share more.

Dlpng will not disclose your personal information to any third party without your permission, except:

1\. Dlpng has been authorized by you or your guardian.

2\. The disclosure of Dlpng is required by the judicial or administrative authorities in accordance with statutory procedures;

3\. When Dlpng brings a lawsuit or arbitration to the user to protect its own legal rights and interests;

4\. In accordance to the terms of service and license agreement between you and Dlpng;

5\. Other circumstances prescribed by laws and regulations.

#### Use of cookies and web beacons

Cookies can help the platform identify users and count the number of users, which are often used by platforms to determine whether the user who has completed the application has logged in. Dlpng promises that research on Cookie information will only be used to improve service/product quality and optimize user experience. If you do not want your personal information to be kept in cookies, you can configure the browser by selecting "reject cookies" or "notify you when the platform sends cookies". Since Dlpng's service is implemented by supporting cookies, after you completely shut down the cookie, it may affect your access to Dlpng or the Dlpng service. When you do not disable cookies, you may be prompted to retain user information the next time you enter the platform through a simplified login (such as automatic login). The method and purpose of Dlpng using web beacons are the same as cookies.

#### Modification of the privacy protection policy

Dlpng shall have the right to modify any provision of the "privacy policy" at any time. Once the content of the privacy policy changes, Dlpng will announce its modifications to the “privacy policy” on the Dlpng platform. This publishing behavior is considered to be a notification by Dlpng to you to modify your content. Dlpng can also prompt users to modify content in other appropriate ways. If you do not agree with Dlpng's changes to the terms of this privacy policy, you have the right to stop using Dlpng’s services. If you continue to use the Dlpng’s services, you will be deemed to have received changes made by Dlpng to the terms of this agreement.
